<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on bruce&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on bruce&#39;s blog</description>
    <image>
      <title>bruce&#39;s blog</title>
      <url>https://brucehrwang.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://brucehrwang.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:06:30 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mechanisitic Interpretability</title>
      <link>https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/mechanistic_interpretability/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2023 18:06:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/mechanistic_interpretability/</guid>
      <description>In this blog, I will introduce a research direction focusing on mechanistic interpretability. This holds significant potential to revolutionize the existing landscape of AI.
Chris Olah drew a compelling analogy when he likened mechanistic interpretability to the process of reverse engineering a compiled binary computer program.
Reverse Engineer Neural Networks
&amp;ldquo;Mechanistic interpretability aims to reverse engineer neural networks, much like the process of reverse engineering a compiled binary computer program. In essence, the parameters of a neural network can be viewed as a binary computer program operating on a specialized virtual machine known as a neural network architecture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to SSH into your PC at home</title>
      <link>https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 18:06:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://brucehrwang.github.io/posts/ssh/</guid>
      <description>In this blog, I will introduce the method I use to ssh into my pc at home. I built my PC back in 2020 so that I would have a little more computing power at my fignertips when I need it. My hope was to avoid having to pay for cloud computing services for my deep learning and CUDA projects. Being someone who enjoys working at a library, I would like to be able to connect to my PC remotely.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
